Jai Jai friend Friends, my insurance wala is
serving you
24*
every time Friends,
tomorrow you can get an offer
which you can get by investing in life insurance
up to 25% discount Friends,
if you
get
GST tax also,
you can get health insurance by
IC Loard, your plan name is Elevate
Elevate Plan, you can buy this
plan also by 15 minutes, buy health
insurance by ICICI Loard, plan name is Elevate Elevate Plan, you can buy this plan also by 15 minutes, buy health
insurance by ICICI Loard, plan name is Elevate Elevate Plan, you can get this
payment by ICICI Loard, plan name is Elevate Elevate Plan,
you can get this payment by ICICI Loard,
if
you ask for an organization policy, if
you buy a three year policy, you will get 15%
discount and if you buy a three year policy, you will get
5% discount, if you buy a three year policy, you will get
20% up to 20% discount
Friends, this offer is only on Durga Puja,
you can give it to me on Durga Puja, but not on GST,
Friends, if you want health insurance, you can
not get it immediately today,
this plan is available in the industry  First, you can check the ICICI Lottery
Elevate plan by going to Google and
comparing it with other companies and ICICI Lottery
Elevate plan Basic
and other companies.
You can check the plan by burning the full price for 15 minutes, there will be no
inconvenience.
Friends, just
wait, you will get this offer on Durga Puja.
Jai Jagannath friends, may you get the blessings of the mother.